Hello friends, my name is Sachin, and
today I'm back with a video. Click here.
So friends, today we're going to talk
about Tata AIG's Medicare Premier. This is a health
insurance plan that offers so
many benefits that you might get tired of hearing about it.
Many people come to us and say they
want the best health insurance. So, as of
today, on the
day this video is being uploaded,
if I were to pick out my top two or three favorite
plans, this is the
plan. It has all the features
that are currently available in any base plan. It also has
matriculation coverage. So, if you
watch this video completely, you'll realize
how many benefits are available in this plan,
which is very difficult to find in a single company. So,
let's start our
review of this plan.
First, friends, let's talk about the
time savings available in it. Here, the plan ranges from ₹5,000 to ₹
10 lakh.  ₹1500000 20 lakh 25 people and in this
way this line can apply up to ₹5000000,
meaning Prime starts from Rs 5 lakh
and you can take MS Word within it up to ₹50
Dear Boss, let's
talk about performance, friends, these are such expenses
when you were not admitted in the hospital, you had
given some money as fees to the doctors,
you had bought some medicines from the market, you had got
some diagnostic tests done, so
whatever expenses are incurred in this way,
see Jupiter Prince, and
after that you were admitted in the hospital, similarly
when you got discharged from the hospital and
came home, the doctor would have
given you some medicines that you have to
take, in this way you would have followed some doctors, in that way
you would have faculty, that money is incurred,
along with that you have got some medical tests done,
after recovery, when you have come home from the hospital, then all
such expenses are
called postposition expenses, so in this way the
expenses of seven days before and 90 days after  You are
given reimbursement in this plan.
Talking about room rent, friends, there is no
room rent limit here.
You can comfortably take single rooms, private rooms, deluxe rooms
here. This makes the plan very
special. Talking about treatment,
friends, see, treatments are
available here. These are such treatments
where you do
not need 24-hour stay. You get admitted
to the hospital in the morning and you get discharged in the evening and come back
home. Mostly,
some procedures i.e. surgeries are easy in this,
like if I talk about cataract,
some removal surgery, kidney stone
surgery, there are seasonal surgeries in this
and there are 541 such procedures. The
list of these can be found on their website
or if you want to ask for it, then
I will provide you this list.
Talking about no claim bonus,
friends, this also makes Spain very good
that you get a no claim bonus of 50% here.
For example, if you  If you
buy an airplane worth Rs 10 lakh, then next year
it will become worth Rs 15 lakh
because a no-claim bonus of Rs 5 lakh will be
added to it. Similarly, if you do
not claim again next year, another Rs 5 lakh will be added to your policy. That means,
your total policy of Rs
10 lakh will now become worth Rs 2000000 after two years.
₹1000000 will be
shown as the amount and a bonus of Rs 10 will be shown.
Talking about the restoration benefit,
friends, that too is quite good and quite
unique here. Suppose you have a policy of Rs 10 lakh
and your friend gets exhausted,
then the company will give you Rs 1000000 again
and will not wait for it to get exhausted.
Suppose the first claim comes for Rs 3 lakh, then
Rs 7 lakh is available to you now. This is
not available separately
because if your restoration has already been done.
Restoration of Rs 10 lakh is also available there,
so you have a total of Rs 17 lakh
available in that year, but under no condition the
company will give you a claim of more than Rs 10 lakh.
Now you
can spend Rs 17 lakh in the entire year, but the
value of any one bill should not exceed Rs 10 lakh.
Along with this,
you are also given
cover on this, but if any such condition
arises that it is also equipped with a sanction note, then there should be
a gap in the flight country,
otherwise it will not work for you, same person or similar. Let's move ahead,
friends, if we talk about ambulance cover here, then
you will get a cover of Rs 5000 for every
hospitalization, which means every time
you can deduct Rs 5000 from the company for ambulance charges, there is
no limit on this, there
is a question of entry limit, friends, so anyone here from 18
years to 65 years of age can take
this policy.  You can buy this and if we
talk about children, then suppose you
already have a policy, then your 91st
child is born in your house, then you
can add it here and at the same time,
your dependent children can remain covered under this policy for
25 years. After 25 years,
a new policy will be offered to them.
Talking about domestic hospitalization,
friends, that is also available here and that is covered for the
entire time.
Friends, what happens is that suppose there is no
hospital available near you
or the patient has any
such condition that he is
not fit to go to the hospital, then the doctor tries to get
you treated at home.
There you will be given the facility of nursing care,
like there is some setup of a hospital,
there is massage, there are some monitors, the
doctor will do it, maybe you have to install an oxygen machine, you may have to use a
machine on your hair, so there
you will have to go to a proper hospital, like this, it is only for three days,
if this thing happens for more than three days, then
you will have to pay commission.  You
can play a significant role friends and at the same time let me
tell you that if you are
taking a policy and you want to
cover multiple family members then
you can cover up to seven people in one policy, you
can live yourself,
your spouse can be added in it,
then you can add three children in it and you
can also add two dependent parents in it. Talking about health checkup benefit
friends, here you get 1% of the sum insured
whose maximum limit is
Rs.10000, that is, if suppose you have
taken a policy of Rs.2000000 then one
percent becomes Rs.20 thousand but
in this condition the company will give you maximum Rs.10000 only,
so you can claim it every year
and even if it was useful for your illnesses,
you will still play it and you will keep getting it
and even if you play it now then
none of your sum assured
decreases because now the time
is left, okay so whatever you  There is a
healthcare benefit in this, which you will keep getting every year
and if we talk about both the covers,
friends, then that is also available here on time injury
and donor cover means that
friends, if you have such a
critical situation that you have to
donate an organ from someone,
suppose it has to be removed or
you have to take a liver, then the person from whom
you have taken the organ is also treated here,
their surgery is also done here,
so the surgery cost of the donor will also be
covered here, if we talk about the settings open
facility, friends, there are many
such diseases in which the doctor does
some surgery on you, that you have to get
this surgery done, or you have to take this
treatment, it is possible that
you may not agree with the opinion of the doctor who has told you this, then
you can
take a consultation from any panel doctor of 181, friends,
you will get that here and it can be for any disease, there is
no special interest for that, so you can also get this facility in
your policy  You can avail global
cover. Friends, this is a
feature which I have
not seen in any other company till now. Here, if
suppose you have any disease in India,
any
disease, and you want to get its
treatment, you can go abroad and get it. The
treatment there may
not be good in India, but you may get it better there in some other country. So,
if you have any such
problem and you want, then you can
go abroad and get treatment. This
policy will cover you there as well, but
the problem is that whatever the disease is, it is
very important to be diagnosed in India. Keep this in
mind. Talking about this treatment,
friends, this treatment is
available there. If
during the treatment you are given any Ayurvedic
medicines, Siddhartha,
Unani or Homeopathy, then
that too will be covered here till the end of the time.
Talking about vaccination cover,
friends, this also makes this line quite unique.
Here you get ₹5000 for
vaccination coverage. If you have
taken the policy, then you  Anti-rabies vaccine
alien, that is, for internal bites,
dog bites, cat bites, these anti-
rabies vaccine actions, you
can get them from here on the first day itself and if you
want to get more vaccinations for hepatitis B or HPV virus, then there is a waiting period of 2 years
here, after that you can also get that here and
you can claim up to ₹5000 for it. If I
talk about bariatric surgery,
friends, then this plan also makes a lot of units
because here the owner has
taken a policy and his weight has increased a lot
and the doctors say that
due to weight you can also get other diseases,
so we will have to reduce your belly fat, that is, the
fat accumulated on the stomach, through
surgery, so for this,
this barricading surgery is done, then
its cover will also be given to you here till the time, if
I talk about Delhi Cash Set,
friends, then that is also available here,
if you choose a sharing room, then you will get it
here at 0.25  You will understand that for
example, if we have taken a policy of Rs 10 lakh,
then 0.2 percent is ₹2000, but
here the maximum limit is ₹2000, which
means you have taken a policy and you take a sharing
room instead of a single private room, then you are saving the company's money,
so here the company will give you an
extra benefit of ₹2000 in your account.
Similarly, if in this policy,
suppose there is any child whose age is
less than 12 years and he
needs admission in the hospital, then it is
possible that any adult member will
need his care, so you will be
given ₹2000 for that also, that
whichever adult is clearing here, there are
14 mothers and 14 fathers, so it is possible that
they too may be incurring loss due to their work,
hence the company will
give you an extra ₹2000 and no
company will charge extra money for this.  There is an
investment feature within the policy as well,
but suppose you have
taken any sharing accommodation for your child as well, then
₹2000 there and ₹2000 here, so in total
you will get this cover of Delhi worth ₹4000.
Talking about hearing aid cover,
friends, many people face such problems
that they have to wear hearing aids
or they hear hard, so
its facility is also available here.
You can avail this cover up to ₹10000 every three years. The
actual
cost consideration is this look, that is ₹10000 or
less. Suppose you get a loan of ₹15000, then 50% of it i.e. ₹7000 will be given here or if you get a loan of ₹
30000, then 50% of it i.e. ₹15000 will be given
here or if it
comes for ₹30000, then
50% of it i.e. ₹15000 will be given here, but
in that condition, you will be given a maximum of ₹10000.
Talking about in-patient dental treatment
Friends, it is available here.
Suppose due to an accident,
due to an injury or due to some illness,
suppose you are admitted in the hospital and
given dental treatment, then that will also be
covered here. Under that, it
is necessary for you to take NSC, for this, that means Vivo
Shiksha medicine. If the doctor has given you anesthesia
and you are undergoing dental treatment, then
that too will be covered here.
Talking about compassionate travel, friends, first let me tell
you what happens. Suppose you
live in any city and you have gone to another city for
some work or for studies
and you fall ill there
or suppose an accident happens, then
what will happen for that? There is
no one to share your expenses there, so
in this condition, if your hospital expenses are
more than what you can bear and your favorite member of the family, that is, your
parents, comes to share your expenses, whether he
comes by train or he travels by train, then he will be provided with
economic class.  Any
hair or rail ticket up to a
maximum of Rs 20,000 will be
replaced here. Friends, if I
talk about this policy, you know that the Tata
Ace brand is a very good brand and people
trust it a lot. So if I talk about their
service, then here is their claim service. They do
not give their claim service in the hands of any third party. They themselves
settle your claims. Moving ahead, friends, let's talk about the
timely benefits. This
benefit of theirs is also quite unique. You must have seen
that many such policies are available
in the market where this benefit is not covered
in the Parliament. So,
what happens in it is that let's say you have
cotton, also love poetry, love se, happy kids, have been
tested sand, these are some extra
items. Friends, the company
never pays for this, or if they do, then
you will have to add a separate ad for it,
but here it
is inbuilt within the policy itself, meaning that you will
not have to pay any money for these things. Income tax
benefit  If I talk about it friends, then whatever
premium you have paid here, under the addition in the Income Tax Act, you will get tax
benefit on it. If we
talk about accidental death benefit in the Income Tax rules, then
friends, this is also a very unique
point in it. In the other policies that you will see,
you have to take that benefit by paying extra money here.
If the male
who had taken the policy here
dies due to any reason due to an
accident, then whatever time period
you had left for, suppose you had taken a policy of 10 lakhs or
20 lakhs, then
whatever money you had taken here,
that money will be deposited in your nominee's
account, but
you have to keep in mind that it will
not work on dependents, it will work only on idiots, the
premium becomes free.
Friends, here in this, it
means that if you have taken the policy
in four years, it should have been taken in 65 years
and gradually your premium
increases here, okay, every 5  The premium increases after a year,
if you reach the age of 71 and then
turn 75, then the
premium of 71 years will be
charged here, after that the
premium will stop increasing, so this
also makes this policy quite unique, if I
talk about emergency air ambulance,
friends, then that too is at the level here, it is
of Rs 5 lakh and this is also available now, if
you ever need an emergency air ambulance,
then you can take cover up to ₹5000 here
and this cover of yours will
not be removed, this is being given to you as an add-on,
which is within this policy itself,
you do
not have to pay extra money for this, if I
talk about prolonged hospitalization, friends, then that
is also available here, if you suppose
this hospitalization, whoever has taken the policy,
his hospitalization is more than a few, then
here one percent of sum
assured will be given to you, meaning if there are 10
Rakhi polices, then Rs.10000 one  It will be given to you
in the form of lump sum and investment. Let's move ahead
friends, let's talk about maternity benefit
friends, so if you have
taken a policy and a daughter is born in your family, then
you can claim up to Rs 60,000 here
and at the same time, if a son is born, then
you can claim up to Rs 50,000 here.
Also, there
is a waiting period of 400 years here friends, the
policy you have taken will be 14 years old from the policy,
after that you can claim
and the most important thing is that there is no
limit on delivery allowances here,
like in many policies, we
can cover up to two children, but there is
no limit here, along with the
waiting rate here, single females can also be covered,
meaning many policies are such
that it is necessary for the husband and wife to be under the policy
and then you have to
cover the waiting period, if I know any
single female lady has taken this policy,
suppose today she is unmarried and her  Her age is 20
years, she has taken a policy and she
continues the policy and the owner gets
married at the age of 25, okay,
and the next year she has a baby,
so there she has covered a
waiting period of 26 years, that is, six years,
whereas for the company I only
need a waiting period of four years, and here, while
living with her husband, she also has a
potato, so here you see that even if there is a
single female, she will
get the medium benefit here
because she had purchased the policy earlier. If I
talk about newborn baby cover, friends, then it
is available here. If
you have
taken the ladyfinger benefit above, then
you will also get the cover for that baby,
suppose they also get some treatment
or they are kept in the nursery,
then in the same way, here they will also be given Rs 10,000 for their
treatment.
Talk about first year vaccination separately, friends, if you have
taken maternity benefit, then you will also know
that the small ones  Children are given
BCG vaccine, dipepta vaccine and there are many
such vaccines which are
given to children within the first year, so for the first year
also you will be given money for the cover of the child,
Rs.10000 will be given if you have
any voice or Rs.15000 will be given
for the girl child if you have
taken maternity benefit, so talking about OPD,
friends, here also this plan has become
quite unique because of this, it is
also available here, ₹5000 will be given to you every year
for OPD, in which you
can take doctor's fees, reimbursement of medicines,
you can also take money for email ore,
but this coverage will not be valid for the first 2 years,
from the third year you will be given this benefit every year,
similarly
if I talk about dental care, then
Rs.10000 is available here and here also
you will not get it for the first 2 years, so you will get it
from one year, suppose now you get a root canal done.  If your
teeth fall out or you get your teeth
capped, then there are
many such treatments
which are required for your teeth and they
cost a lot, so that is also an
emphasis here, but if we talk about policy discount from the third year, then
if you take Ghoshal's policy in one go, then
you will get a discount of 5 percent
and in the same way, if you buy 3 years' policy
together, then you will get a discount of 10
percent which is total free.
Moving ahead, friends, let us now talk about
family floater discount, if
suppose you
take the policy as an individual policy, then whatever the
result of the individual was coming and you have taken it
in the footer by taking individual name, then
you will get a discount of 40% from the individual rate,
if you have taken the policy for two members, then you will
get a discount of 8 percent, if you have taken the policy for three members, then you will
get a discount of 32% if you have set more than three members in the policy,
for example, if
And an individual was
getting a premium of Rs 15,000 and if you
added another individual, then
there too they would get Rs 15,000 individually,
but if you included them in the plan, then
whoever was becoming the PM for both of them would get
Rs 3,000, so you will get a 20% discount there.
Similarly, if there are three members, then it will be Rs
28 per cent and if there are more than three, then it will be Rs 32 per
cent. Let's move ahead, friends, talking about
diagnostics, friends, till now
I have not seen this feature in any company,
so you should understand it carefully, first of all, if a
doctor advises you that you have
this disease, any serious disease and you have these
symptoms, then you should get a medical checkup done, so
friends, here it is
written in this way, swelling on the brain,
imaging is fine, CT scan done, CT
biopsy done, liver biopsy done,
pattern cream done, stomach CT done, okay, so
friends, these are the
examinations which are very expensive, which are done
for father diagnostics.
Diagnostic tests are done for some serious diseases like some cancer diseases,
if suppose any such serious
disease  There is a brightness, whoever has
taken the policy, then you will have to take admission and get
its treatment,
you will definitely get it under the policy, but if
suppose your report comes negative, then
you have spent a lot of money on OPD basis,
if this report comes negative
then you can take its investment up to Rs 25000 here, so
friends, this
unique feature makes this policy very special,
so I was telling you that you
might get tired of hearing the features of this policy,
so see how many
features are available in this policy,
so let's move ahead friends, now let's talk about the
experience, friends, here the
waiting period of two years is pre-
existing, which means you should have had
some disease already, like suppose you were
diabetic, had BP problem,
thyroid, you are fine or you have
ever been to Bigg Boss, then this is some
such disease which you already have
before taking the policy, then this disease will be
covered here, but it will be talked about for two years,
so  There is a waiting period of two years here,
some people have front gate of this
like cataract, heart disease,
joint replacement, stone,
sinus surgery and problem towards uterus,
uterus removal, sinus
for lips, kidney stones, so
these are some such problems friends which are
covered after 2 years and in the same way it
is in this policy as well and in the journal also you will get a
waiting period of almost 2 years,
almost every moment Sikandar friends, here there is a waiting period of 30 days,
you will
not get it for any disease here, except accidental cover,
if there is hospitalization due to accident,
even if it happens
after one or two days of taking the policy, then
this policy will work for you, but
you will not get cover for any disease in the first 30 days,
which is four years in almost every policy,
so friends, the waiting
period here is of matter coverage, I have already
told you earlier, initial 2 years
means the initial two years which  There
is a waiting period here for that OPD coverage.
I told you that whatever OPD
is introduced or dental OPD, whether it is your
normal OPD, it will be covered only after 2 years.
If you
want to know more about this policy, then you
can go to its terms and conditions section and
read its policy C buildings, which is
quite simple and easy. I will give you the
description link for it. Now you can
download it here and read it comfortably.
I will also give you the brochure,
so you can go there and see it.
Moving ahead, friends, you can also connect with me.
You ask me a lot of questions
and I provide you with many
mediums, you can ask them. You
can WhatsApp me on this number. Okay,
you can follow me on Instagram under the name of
Insurance. Then you
can follow me on Facebook under the name of Sachin.
facebook.com
We have a Telegram group under the name of Slice Insurance, in
which you get
all the updates related to insurance from time to time.
You can follow me on Twitter under the name of
In One Sachin.  By name and
if suppose you want to ask something,
want to share the document of any disease, want to share your policy document, want to
ask me something
about that then you can write me an email, you
can share the email mode with me, contact other tutorials
also in the name of Sachin, so friends I hope
you have understood some plan and
liked it because other plans are quite unique,
so do not forget to share it with your friends
so that your friends
also get the knowledge that
such good plans are also available in the market and
of very good companies and at the same time friends do
not forget to like this video,
I will meet you in the next video, my name is
Sachin Verma, thank you very much for watching this video.